empiretoday.com 2018-08-27

# Privacy Policy | Empire Today

Effective Date: This Privacy Policy was last revised November 1, 2017

To print our Privacy Policy, [**click here**](https://prod-01-empiretodaycontent-app.azureedge.net/assets/pdfs/empire-printable-privacy-policy.pdf). To print our Terms of Use, [**click here**](https://prod-01-empiretodaycontent-app.azureedge.net/assets/pdfs/empire-printable-terms-of-use.pdf). To receive copies of both documents by e-mail, **click here**.

**Introduction and Overview**

Welcome! You have arrived at a web site that is owned and operated by Empire Today, LLC (“ **Company** ”or “ **we** ,” “ **our** ” or “ **us** ”). This “ **Privacy Policy** ” governs your use of any web site, mobile app or other online service (“ **Site** ”)(including, without limitation, both mobile and online versions of our Site), and also applies to your use of interactive features, widgets, plug-ins, applications, content, downloads and/or other services that we own and control and make available through a Site and that posts a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “ **Service** ”), regardless of how you access or use them, whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise. This Privacy Policy explains what information Company collects on the Service, how Company uses that information, under what circumstances we may disclose Personal Information (defined below) to third parties and the Service’s other practices with respect to the collection, use and sharing of your information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to our data collection activities offline or otherwise outside of our Service (unless otherwise specifically stated below), and does not govern the data practices of third parties that may interact with our Service.

**To the extent we provide you notice on our Service of different or additional privacy policies or practices (e.g., at the point of our collection), those additional terms shall govern such data collection and use.**

In addition, please review the Service’s **Terms of Use**, which governs your use of the Service. _By using our Service_ , _you consent to our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use and our collection, use and sharing of your information and data, and other activities, as described below._

You should read this entire Privacy Policy, but below is a list of some of the key topics that are explored in greater detail throughout the Privacy Policy and you can click **here** for a summary of each section of the Privacy Policy. Any capitalized terms have the meanings given to them where defined in the Privacy Policy.

  * We ask you for, and use technology to detect, information about you.
  * Third parties may collect information about you. Their privacy policies, not ours, govern their practices.
  * **Notice to California Residents / Your California Privacy Rights** : California residents may request information about sharing of certain personal information with third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes by contacting us using the methods described below. **Click for more information**.
  * You consent to our practices detailed in this Privacy Policy. To prospectively change your consent, stop using the Service.

**Linkable Table of Contents**

**It is important that you read and understand the entire Privacy Policy before using the Service. To ease review, each section below contains a brief introductory summary and a link to the full explanation. You can click on the headings and the “More” links to be taken to the full explanation. Any capitalized terms that appear in but are not otherwise defined in the introduction are intended to have the meanings given to them elsewhere in the Privacy Policy.**

  1. **What Information Does the Service Collect?**

We collect and receive information about you as you interact with our Service. **More**

    1. **Information You Provide to Us**

We collect certain Personal Information and Demographic Information that you provide to us when you interact with the Service. For example, we may collect this information through various forms and in various places on the Service, including when you make an appointment, from newsletter registration forms, through “contact us” forms, or when you otherwise interact with the Service. **More**

    2. **Information We Collect and Store as You Access and Use the Service**

We may collect certain information from you automatically when you access and use the Service. For example, we may use Tracking Technologies to collect Usage Information based on your Device Identifier for a variety of purposes, including tracking and targeting. You can avoid such tracking by deleting your cookies, following the options provided by third parties discussed in more detail below and stopping use of the Service. **More**

    3. **Information Third Parties Provide About You**

We may obtain information about you from third parties. **More**

    4. **Interactions with Third-Party Services**

If you interact with third-party services, those services may send us information about you and we may send them information about you. **More**

    5. **Information You Provide About a Third Party**

You may provide us information about others, such as when you send a friend a message. If so, the information you provide (names, e-mail addresses, mobile number, etc.) may be used to facilitate the communication, but will not be used for other marketing purposes unless your friend consents. You may be identified to the friend in connection with such message. **More**

  2. **How Do We Use the Information Collected?**

    1. **Use of Information By Us**

We use your Personal Information, Demographic Information and Usage Information for a variety of purposes detailed in this section. **More**

    2. **Advertising, Content Management and Location Based Services**

We use your Personal Information, Demographic Information and Usage Information for services detailed in this section. **More**

    3. **Use of Information For Recruitment Purposes**

If you apply for a job with us, we use the application information for considering you for a position. **More**

  3. **How and When Do We Share Information With Third Parties?**

We may provide your information to third parties under various circumstances detailed in this section. These may include:

    1. **When You Request Information From or Provide Information to Third Parties**  
If you request information from third parties, request that we send information to third parties or interact with third-party services, content, ads or tools (including Facebook and other third party share functionality) we may share your information with such parties and/or they may collect your information directly. **More**

    2. **Third Parties Providing Services on our Behalf**

Our vendors may collect your information or we may share it with them. **More**

    3. **To Protect the Rights of Company and Our Users**

There are a variety of administrative and legal reasons for which we may share some or all of your information. **More**

    4. **Affiliates and Business Transfer**

We may share your information with our affiliates and with third parties in the event of a sale, merger or similar transaction. **More**

    5. **Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions**

Promotions entrants may be required to consent to certain information sharing. **More**

    6. **EEOC/Affirmative Action Reporting**

Certain employment application, self-identifying information (e.g., race and gender) may be shared with the government and other third parties. **More**

  4. **Your California Privacy Rights**

California residents have certain rights regarding our sharing of certain personal information with third parties for direct marketing, and regarding minor’s public postings. **More**

  5. **What About Information I Disclose Publicly or to Others?**

    1. **User-Generated Content and Public Information**

Posting content in public areas makes it available to others. We may share and use your public information for any reason not otherwise prohibited by this Privacy Policy. **More**

    2. **Name and Likeness**

You grant us the right to use your name and likeness in connection with your posting and activities. **More**

  6. **Third-Party Content, Third-Party Services, Social Features, Advertising and Analytics**

We may allow you to access third-party content on the Service, or to link to third-party applications and locations from the Service, but we are not responsible for your interaction with third-party content, apps and locations. **More**

  7. **How Do I Change My Information and Communications Preferences?**

You may change certain portions of your information and communications preferences as more fully detailed in this section. **More**

    1. **Accessing And Changing Information**

    2. **Tracking Technologies Generally**

    3. **Analytics and Interest-Based Advertising**

    4. **Communications and Marketing**

    5. **Contact Us**

  8. **Transfer of Information to the United States**

Data may be transferred to the United States. **More**

  9. **What Should Parents Know About Children?**

We do not intend to collect Personal Information from children. **More**

  10. **What About Security?**

No data security is absolute, but we take reasonable steps to secure data appropriately. **More**

  11. **Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy upon posting of a revised Privacy Policy. However, we will continue to treat your Personal Information under the terms of the privacy policy in effect when it was collected unless you otherwise consent. **More**

**The Full Detailed Privacy Policy**

  1. **What Information Does the Service Collect?**

    1. **Information You Provide to Us**

**Personal Information and Demographic Information**. On the Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain categories of information such as: (1) personally identifiable information, which is information that could reasonably be used to identify you personally, such as your first and last name, e-mail address, home address, and phone number (“ **Personal Information** ”); and (2) demographic information, such as information like your zip code (“ **Demographic Information** ”). Except to the extent required by applicable law, Demographic Information is **“non-Personal Information”** (i.e., data that is not treated as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy). In addition, as permitted by applicable law, Personal Information, once **“de-identified”** (i.e., the removal or modification of personally identifiable elements or the extraction of non-personally identifiable elements) is also non-Personal Information and may be used and shared without obligation to you, except as prohibited by applicable law. To the extent any non-Personal Information is combined by or on behalf of Company with Personal Information Company itself collects directly from you on the Service, Company will treat the combined data as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy. We may collect this information through various forms and in various places on the Service, including when you schedule an in-home consultation/estimate, apply for a position with the Company, complete a survey, through “contact us” forms, or when you otherwise interact with the Service. Providing us with information about yourself is voluntary, but if you choose not to provide certain information you may not be able to take advantage of all of the Service’s features.

We may also collect Personal Information from you offline, such as when you call to schedule an in-home estimate or otherwise call our customer service center. This Privacy Policy generally does not apply to any information collected in these circumstances. However, if we combine Personal Information we collect from you offline with the Personal Information we collect through the Service, we will treat the combined data as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy.

back to top ^
    2. **Information We Collect and Store as You Access and Use the Service**

In addition to any Personal Information or other information that you choose to submit to us via our Service, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically (or passively) store or collect certain information whenever you visit or interact with the Service (“ **Usage Information** ”). This Usage Information may be stored or accessed using a variety of technologies that may be downloaded to your personal computer, browser, laptop, tablet, mobile phone or other device (a “ **Device** ”) whenever you visit or interact with our Service. To the extent we associate Usage Information with your Personal Information we collect directly from you on the Service, we will treat it as Personal Information.

This Usage Information may include:

      * your IP address, UID or other unique identifier (“ **Device Identifier** ”). A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your Device used to access the Service, and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier;
      * your Device functionality (including browser, operating system, hardware, mobile network information);
      * the URL that referred you to our Service;
      * the areas within our Service that you visit and your activities there, including remembering you and your preferences;
      * your Device location;
      * your Device characteristics; and
      * certain other Device data, including the time of day, among other information.

We may use various methods and technologies to store or collect Usage Information (“ **Tracking Technologies** ”). Tracking Technologies may set, change, alter or modify settings or configurations on your Device. A few of the Tracking Technologies include, without limitation, the following (and subsequent technology and methods later developed):

**_Cookies_**. A cookie is a data file placed on a Device when it is used to visit the Service. HTML5 cookies can be programmed through HTML5 local storage and do not require a plug-in. Regular cookies may generally be disabled or removed by tools that are available as part of most commercial browsers, and in some but not all instances can be blocked in the future by selecting certain settings. Each browser you use will need to be set separately and different browsers offer different functionality and options in this regard. Also, these tools may not be effective with regard to HTML5 cookies. Please be aware that if you disable or remove cookies or HTML5 cookies on your Device, some parts of our Service may not function properly, and that when you revisit our Service your ability to limit cookies is subject to your browser settings and limitations.

**_Web Beacons_**. Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as “1x1 GIFs” or “clear GIFs”) may be included in our Service’s pages and messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the Service, to monitor how users navigate the Service, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.

**_Embedded Scripts_**. An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Service, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our web server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Service, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

**_ETag, or entity tag_**. A feature of the cache in browsers. It is an opaque identifier assigned by a web server to a specific version of a resource found at a URL. If the resource content at that URL ever changes, a new and different ETag is assigned. Used in this manner ETags are a form of Device Identifier. ETag tracking may generate unique tracking values even where the consumer blocks HTTP, Flash, and/or HTML5 cookies.

We may use Tracking Technologies for a variety of purposes, including:

**_Strictly Necessary_**. We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that we consider are strictly necessary to allow you to use and access our Service, including cookies required to prevent fraudulent activity, improve security or allow you to make use of appointment scheduling functionality.

**_Performance‑Related_**. We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that are useful in order to assess the performance of the Service, including as part of our analytic practices or otherwise to improve the content, products or services offered through the Service.

**_Functionality‑Related_**. We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that are required to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing the Service, including identifying you when you sign‑in to our Service or keeping track of our specified preferences, including in terms of the presentation of content on our Service.

**_Targeting‑Related_**. We may use Tracking Technologies to deliver content relevant to your interests on our Service and third‑party services based on how you interact with our advertisements or content. This includes using Tracking Technologies to understand the usefulness to you of the content that has been delivered to you.

There may be other Tracking Technologies now and later devised and used by us in connection with the Service. Further, third parties may use Tracking Technologies with our Service. We may not control those Tracking Technologies and we are not responsible for them. However, you consent to potentially encountering third party Tracking Technologies in connection with use of our Service and accept that our statements under this Privacy Policy do not apply to the Tracking Technologies or practices of such third parties.

back to top ^
    3. **Information Third Parties Provide About You**

We may also receive information about you from other sources, such as our third party suppliers and data improvement and other service providers for various purposes, including to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities that may be of interest to you. To the extent we combine information we receive from those sources with your Personal Information we collect on the Service, it will be treated as Personal Information and we will apply this Privacy Policy to such combined information, unless we have disclosed otherwise. In no other circumstances do our statements under this Privacy Policy apply to information we receive about you from third parties.

back to top ^
    4. **Interactions with Third-Party Services**

The Service may now or in the future include functionality that allows certain kinds of interactions between the Service and your account on a third-party web site or application. The use of this functionality may involve the third-party providing certain information, including Personal Information, to us. For example, we may provide third-party services’ interfaces or links on the Service to facilitate your sending a communication from the Service.

For example, we may use third parties to facilitate e-mails, tweets, “likes,” content submissions or postings of comments on Facebook or other social media platforms. We may also enable access to or display of third party content via the Service, that is actually being served or published by the third party, and such third party may be collecting data from you in connection with that content. These third parties may collect and retain any information used or provided in any such communications or other activities and these third parties’ practices are not subject to our Privacy Policy. Company may not control or have access to your communications through these third parties. When you use third-party services, you are using their services and not our Services and they, not we, are responsible for their practices. You should review the applicable third-party privacy policies before using such third-party services in connection with our Service. For more information on third-party services and the policies and activities of third-parties, see “Third Parties Providing Services on Our Behalf” here, and “Third-Party Content, Third-Party Services, Social Features, Advertising and Analytics” here.

back to top ^
    5. **Information You Provide About a Third Party**

You may send someone else a communication from the Service, such as sending an invitation to a friend. If so, the information you provide (names, e-mail addresses, mobile number, etc.) is used to facilitate the communication and is not used by us for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly say otherwise. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on our Service, your e-mail address, mobile number, name or user name and message may be included in the communication sent to your addressee(s). Some of these tools may be third-party tools subject to third-party privacy policies.

back to top ^
  2. **How Do We Use the Information Collected?**

    1. **Use of Information By Us**

We may use information about you, including Personal Information, for any purposes not inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, or our statements at the point of collection, and not prohibited by applicable law, including, without limitation, the following: We may use your Personal Information (this includes your e-mail address, mailing address and telephone number), Demographic Information and/or Usage Information that is subject to this Privacy Policy: (1) to process transactions or provide you with information such as to send you electronic newsletters or to provide you with special offers or promotional and marketing materials on behalf of us or third parties, including to let you know about new products or services or upcoming events; (2) to enable you to participate in a variety of the Service’s features such as to contact you in connection with your appointment scheduled on the Service for an in-person estimate or to enable you to participate in online entry sweepstakes, contests or other promotions; (3) to process your appointment or other request made through the Service, including verifying your information is active and valid; (4) to improve the Service or our services, to customize your experience on the Service, or to serve you specific content that is relevant to you; (5) to contact you with regard to your use of the Service or to provide you with any information or services that you have requested; (6) to contact you, in our discretion, about changes to the Service and/or Service’s policies; (7) for internal business purposes; and (8) for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Please note that information submitted to the Service via a “contact us” or other similar function may not receive a response; however, we may use that information so provided to contact you for marketing purposes unrelated to your inquiry.

back to top ^
    2. **Advertising, Content Management and Location-Based Services**

We may also use your Personal Information, Demographic Information or Usage Information that we collect about you: (1) to provide advertisements or content to you, including based on your activities; (2) to identify your location (e.g., to identify stores near you or offers applicable to you); (3) to understand the usefulness and effectiveness of the advertisements or content that have been delivered to you; and (4) when you comment to or add content to the Service. For more on advertising, see “Third-Party Content, Third-Party Services, Social Features, Advertising and Analytics” here, and for information on your choices regarding advertising, see “How Do I Change My Information and Communications Preferences?” here.

back to top ^
    3. **Use of Information for Recruitment Purposes**

Where you have provided us with Personal Information or Demographic Information as part of an online application for employment or internship, we may use that information in order to allow us to make an informed decision about whether to proceed with your application. We may, as part of this recruitment process, collect information about your education, employment history and similar matters. Where this Personal Information or Demographic Information is considered to be sensitive, you expressly consent to our processing of this information for recruitment purposes by submitting it to us.

back to top ^
  3. **How and When Do We Share Information With Third Parties?**

We may share non-Personal Information, such as aggregated user statistics, with third parties. We may share your Device Identifiers with third parties along with data related to you and your activities. In addition, we may share the information we have collected about you, including Personal Information, as disclosed at the time you provide your information and as described below or otherwise in this Privacy Policy. Company’s sharing of your Personal Information is subject to the following:

    * Marketing: Subject to your communications choices explained here, and the rights of California residents explained here,we may use your Personal Information to send you marketing communications. Company may sell or otherwise share your Personal Information with its affiliates, and with third parties, for their own direct or other marketing purposes. If you are a California resident, you have the right to request additional information. Please see **Section 4** below.
    * Your Disclosure or Consent: As more fully described here (“What About Information I Disclose Publicly or to Others?”) and here (“How and When Do We Share Information With Third Parties?”), your activities on the Service may, by their nature, result in the sharing of your Personal Information with third parties, and by engaging in these activities you consent to that and further sharing, and your Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties. Such third party data receipt and collection is subject to the privacy and business practices of that third party, not Company.

Company may also share any information about you (including, without limitation, Personal Information) for any purposes not in-consistent with this Privacy Policy, or our statements at the point of collection, and not prohibited by applicable law, including, without limitation:

    1. **When You Request Information From or Provide Information to Third Parties**

You may be presented with an option on our Service to receive certain information and/or marketing offers directly from third parties or to have us send certain information to third parties or give them access to it. If you choose to do so, your Personal Information and other information may be disclosed to such third parties and all information you disclose will be subject to the third-party privacy policies and practices of such third parties. In addition, third parties may store, collect or otherwise have access to your information when you interact with their Tracking Technologies, content, tools, apps or ads on our Service or link to them from our Service. This may include using third-party tools such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest or other third-party posting or content sharing tools. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such third parties and, therefore, you should review such third-party privacy policies and practices of such third parties prior to requesting information from or otherwise interacting with them.

back to top ^
    2. **Third Parties Providing Services on Our Behalf**

We may use third-party vendors to perform certain services on behalf of us or the Service, such as hosting the Service, designing and/or operating the Service’s features, tracking the Service’s activities and analytics, and enabling us to send you special offers or perform other administrative services. We may provide these vendors with access to user information, including Device Identifiers and Personal Information, to carry out the services they are performing for you or for us. Third-party analytics and other service providers may set and access their own Tracking Technologies on your Device and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you, potentially including Personal Information, about you. We are not responsible for those third party technologies or activities arising out of them. However, some may offer you certain choices regarding their practices, and information we have been informed of regarding such choices is available **here**. We are not responsible for the effectiveness of or compliance with any third parties’ opt-out options.

back to top ^
    3. **To Protect the Rights of Company and Our Users**

To the fullest extent not prohibited by applicable law, we may also disclose your information if we believe in good faith that doing so is necessary or appropriate to: (i) protect or defend the rights, safety or property of Company or third parties (including through the enforcement of this Policy, our **Terms of Use**, and other applicable agreements and policies); (ii) comply with legal and regulatory obligations and government requests (e.g., pursuant to law enforcement inquiries, subpoenas or court orders); (iii) comply with our obligations and commitments to safeguard the privacy and security of your information; or (iv) prevent unauthorized, improper or illegal activities on the Service. Further, we may disclose information about you as otherwise permitted under our Terms of Use or as specifically disclosed when we collect information from you. Additionally, if you notify us that you believe your rights have been violated in connection with the Service or another user of the Service, we may disclose information about you to the extent necessary to evaluate and respond to your concern. To the fullest extent not prohibited by applicable law, we have complete discretion in electing to make or not make such disclosures, and to contest or not contest requests for such disclosures, all without notice to you.

back to top ^
    4. **Affiliates and Business Transfer**

We may share your information, including your Device Identifiers and Personal Information, Demographic Information and Usage Information with our parent, subsidiaries and affiliates. We also reserve the right to disclose and transfer all such information: (i) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Service or applicable database; or (ii) in connection with a merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our interests and/or assets or other corporate change, including during the course of any due diligence process.

back to top ^
    5. **Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions**

We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (“ **Promotion** ”) through the Service that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including allowing the sponsor of the Promotion to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion’s official rules, such as on a winners list. By entering, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that Promotion, which may include consent to additional or differing data practices from those contained in this Privacy Policy. Please review those rules carefully.

back to top ^
    6. **EEOC / Affirmative Action Reporting**

In conjunction with laws and regulations enforced by the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (“ **EEOC** ”), the Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs (“ **OFCCP** ”) and similar state and local regulatory agencies, we may ask you to provide us with self-identifying information (such as veteran status, gender and ethnicity). Providing such self-identifying information is voluntary, but if you do provide us with such information, we may submit that information to the EEOC, the OFCCP and similar state and local regulatory agencies or otherwise use or disclose it for business-related purposes, including, without limitation, responding to information requests, fulfilling regulatory reporting requirements and defending against employment related complaints.

back to top ^
  4. **Your California Privacy Rights**.

We may from time to time elect to share certain “personal information” (as defined by California’s “Shine The Light” law) about you with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents who have supplied personal information, as defined in the statute, to us to, under certain circumstances, to request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If this applies, you may obtain the categories of personal information shared and the names and addresses of all third parties that received personal information for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately prior calendar year (e.g. requests made in 2017 will receive information about 2016 sharing activities). To make such a request, please provide sufficient information for us to determine if this applies to you, attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. To make such a request (limit one request per year), please send an e-mail to PrivacyPolicy@Empire-Today.com, with “California Privacy Rights” as the subject line or mail us a letter to: 333 Northwest Avenue, Northlake, IL 60164, Attention: Marketing Inquiries. You must include your full name, e-mail address, postal address, and zip code in your request. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year **,** and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address or mail address.

California minors should see “What Should Parents Know About Children?” here regarding removal of certain content they have posted.

back to top ^
  5. **What About Information I Disclose Publicly or to Others?**

    1. **User-Generated Content and Public Information**

The Service may permit you to submit ideas, photographs, user profiles, writings, music, video, audio recordings, computer graphics, pictures, data, questions, comments, suggestions or other content, including Personal Information (collectively, “ **User Content** ”), such as on blogs and message boards or through our “contact us” functionality. We or others may store, display, reproduce, publish, distribute or otherwise use User Content online or offline in any media or format (currently existing or hereafter developed) and may or may not attribute it to you. Others may have access to this User Content and may have the ability to share it with third parties. Please think carefully before deciding what information you share, including Personal Information, in connection with your User Content. Please note that Company does not control who will have access to the information that you choose to make public, and cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy or keep it secure. We are not responsible for the privacy or security of any information that you make publicly available on the Service or what others do with information you share with them on the Service. We are not responsible for the accuracy, use or misuse of any User Content that you disclose or receive from third parties through the Service. California minors should see “What Should Parents Know About Children” here regarding removal of certain content they have posted on our Service.

back to top ^
    2. **Name and Likeness**

As permitted by applicable law, except where we have otherwise explicitly agreed, we may also publish your name, voice, likeness and other Personal Information that is part of your User Content, and we may use the content, or any portion of the content, for advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities, without remuneration, or other obligation to you. For full terms and conditions regarding User Content you submit to the Service, please review our **Terms of Use**.

back to top ^
  6. **Third-Party Content, Third-Party Services, Social Features, Advertising and Analytics.**

The Service may contain content that is supplied by a third-party, and those third parties may collect usage data and your Device Identifier when such content is served to you. Associated third-party services may also be available via the Service. We are not responsible for the data collection and privacy practices employed by such third parties or their services and they may themselves be collecting data from you and may be sharing it with us and/or others. These third parties and their services may also associate their Tracking Technologies with you, track you across sites and time, serve you their own ads (including Interest-based Ads (defined below)) and may or may not have their own published privacy policies.

In addition, when you are on the Service you may be directed to other services that are operated and controlled by third parties that we do not control. For example, if you “click” on a link, the “click” may take you off the Service onto a different site or service. We encourage you to note when you leave our Service and to review the third-party privacy policies of all third-party locations and exercise caution in connection with them.

Be sure to review any available privacy policies and notices before submitting any Personal Information to a third party or its services, or otherwise interacting with third-party services or other locations you link to from our Service, and exercise caution in connection with them. We are not responsible for the availability, completeness or accuracy of such third parties’ policies or notices.

Company may engage and work with third parties to serve advertisements on Company’s behalf on the Service, and/or on other websites, mobile apps and online services, and/or to provide analytics about the use of the Service and the performance of Company’s ads and content on the Service and on third-party services. In addition, Company may participate in online advertising networks and exchanges that display relevant advertisements to the Company visitors, on the Service and on third-party services, based on user interests as reflected in their browsing of the Service and certain third-party services. These entities may use cookies and other Tracking Technologies to automatically collect information about you and your activities, such as registering a unique identifier for your device and tying that to your online activities on and off of the Service. Company may use this information to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on the Service and third-party services and better understand your online activity.

Some information about your use of the Service and certain third-party services may be collected using Tracking Technologies across time and services and used by Company and third parties for purposes such as to associate different devices you use, and deliver relevant and retargeted ads (“Interest-based Ads”) and/or other content to you on the Service and certain third-party services. You may have certain choices regarding these activities as explained in the next section.

As permitted by applicable law, Company is not responsible for third parties or third-party services associated with advertising and analytics services, and related tracking activities. Consult their privacy policies and notices for information on their practices and see “How Do I Change My Information and Communications Preferences?” here regarding certain choices some of them may offer you.

back to top ^
  7. **How Do I Change My Information and Communications Preferences?**

    1. **Accessing And Changing Information**

The Service may provide web pages or other mechanisms allowing you to delete, correct or update some of the Personal Information you have provided Company. Company will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in Company’s then-active databases as soon as practicable, but it is not always possible to completely change, remove or delete all of your information or public postings from Company’s databases (California minors see “What Should Parents Know About Children” here and residual and/or cached data may remain archived thereafter. Further, we reserve the right to retain data (i) as required by applicable law; and (ii) for so long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes for which the data is retained as permitted by applicable law (e.g., business records).

back to top ^
    2. **Tracking Technologies Generally**

Regular cookies may generally be disabled or removed by tools available as part of most commercial browsers, and in some instances blocked in the future by selecting certain settings. Browsers offer different functionalities and options so you may need to set them separately. Also, tools from commercial browsers may not be effective with regard to Flash cookies (also known as locally shared objects), HTML5 cookies or other Tracking Technologies. For information on disabling Flash cookies, go to Adobe’s website [**https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-third-party-local-shared.html**](https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-third-party-local-shared.html) **.** Please be aware that if you disable or remove these technologies some parts of the Service may not work and that when you revisit the Service your ability to limit browser-based Tracking Technologies is subject to your browser settings and limitations.

Your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “Do Not Track” signal to online services you visit. Note, however, Company currently does not alter Company’s practices when Company receives a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser. Some third parties, however, may also offer you choices regarding their Tracking Technologies. One way to potentially identify cookies on our Site is to add the free Ghostery plug-in to your browser ( **www.ghostery.com** ), which according to Ghostery will display for you traditional, browser-based cookies associated with the web sites (but not mobile apps) you visit and privacy and opt-out policies and options of the parties operating those cookies. Company is not responsible for the completeness or accuracy of this tool or third party choice notices or mechanisms. For specific information on some of the choice options offered by third party analytics and advertising providers, see the next section.

back to top ^
    3. **Analytics and Interest-Based Advertising**

Company may use Google Analytics, Adobe Analytics or other service providers for analytics services. These analytics services may use cookies and other Tracking Technologies to help Company analyze how users use the Service. Information generated by these services ( _e.g._ , your IP address and other Usage Information) may be transmitted to and stored by Google Analytics, Adobe Analytics and other service providers on servers in the U.S. (or elsewhere) and these service providers may use this information for purposes such as evaluating your use of the Service, compiling statistic reports on the Service’s activity, and providing other services relating to Service activity and other Internet usage. You may exercise choices regarding the use of cookies from Google Analytics by going to [**https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout**](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) or downloading the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on. You may exercise choices regarding the use of cookies from Adobe Analytics by going to [**http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html**](https://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html)under the section labeled “Tell our customers not to measure your use of their websites or tailor their online ads for you.”

Certain companies may participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“ **DAA** ”) AdChoices Program and may display an Advertising Option Icon for Interest-based Ads that links to an opt-out tool which allows you to exercise certain choices regarding targeting. You can learn more about the DAA AdChoices Program at [**http://www.youradchoices.com/**](http://www.youradchoices.com/) and its opt-out program for mobile apps at [**http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices**](http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices) **.** In addition, certain advertising networks and exchanges may participate in the Network Advertising Initiative (“ **NAI** ”). NAI has developed a tool that allows consumers to opt out of certain Interest-based Ads delivered by NAI members’ ad networks. To learn more about opting out of such targeted advertising or to use the NAI tool, see [**http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). Please be aware that, even if you are able to opt out of certain kinds of Interest-based Ads, you will continue to receive non-targeted ads. Further, opting out of one or more NAI or DAA members only means that those selected members should no longer under the DAA / NAI rules deliver certain targeted ads to you. This will affect this and other services, but does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content and/or ads ( _e.g._ , from other ad networks). Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different Device or web browser(s), or use a non-browser-based method of access (e.g., mobile app), your NAI / DAA browser-based opt-out may not, or may no longer, be effective. Mobile device opt-outs will not affect browser-based Interest-based Ads even on the same device, and you must opt-out separately for each device. Company is not responsible for the effectiveness of, or compliance with, any third-parties’ opt-out options or programs or the accuracy of their statements regarding their programs. However, Company supports the ad industry’s **2009 Self-regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising (**[ **http://www.iab.net/media/file/ven-principles-07-01-09.pdf**](http://www.iab.net/media/file/ven-principles-07-01-09.pdf) **)** and expects that ad networks Company directly engages to serve you Interest-based Ads will do so as well, though Company cannot guaranty their compliance.

back to top ^
    4. **Communications and Marketing**

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as your contact information provided as part of registration. You may provide registration updates and changes by contacting us at [mailto:PrivacyPolicy@Empire-Today.com](mailto:PrivacyPolicy@Empire-Today.com). If so, we will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then active databases as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases and that residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons. Also, if you have made any public postings on the Service such as in forums or blogs, these communications cannot generally be removed. You can opt out of receiving certain promotional communications (emails or text messaging), and non-promotional text alerts, from Company at any time by (i) for promotional e-mails, by following the instructions as provided in emails to click on the unsubscribe link, or if available by changing your communication preferences by logging onto your account; and (ii) for text messages, by following the instructions as provided in text messages from Company to text the word, “STOP”. Please note that your opt-out is limited to the Device, e-mail address or phone number used and will not affect subsequent subscriptions. If you opt-out of only certain communications, other subscriptions may continue. Even if you opt out of receiving promotional communications, Company may, subject to applicable law, continue to send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account, transactions, servicing, or Company’s ongoing business relations; PROVIDED, HOWEVER THAT IF YOU text the word, “STOP”, IN REPLY TO A NON-PROMOTIONAL TEXT, OR OTHERWISE OPT-OUT FROM A NON-PROMOTIONAL TEXT PROGRAM YOU HAVE JOINED, YOU WILL BE UNSUBSCRIBED FROM THAT ALERT PROGRAM UNLESS YOU RE-JOIN. YOU CONSENT TO RECEIVE A TEXT CONFIRMING OF YOUR OPT-OUT FROM A TEXT PROGRAM. 

To choose to no longer receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events, please call us at 1-800-588-2300 and we will place you on our “Do Not Call” list. Although we may ask for your name, address, and telephone number, we will accept your request even if you only provide your telephone number. When we receive your request, the telephone number you provide is added to our “Do Not Call” list in 7-15 business days. Please note that even if you choose to be placed on our “Do Not Call” list, Company reserves the right to contact you via telephone regarding any scheduled appointments or services provided. If you subsequently subscribe to text alerts or to receive a marketing call that will override the “Do Not Call” list. 

back to top ^
    5. **Contact Us**

You may contact us regarding privacy inquires and marketing preferences at PrivacyPolicy@Empire-Today.com with Attention: Privacy Policy in the subject line.

back to top ^
  8. **Transfer of Information to the United States.**

Our Service is operated in the United States and intended for users located in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect, including Personal Information, will be transferred to, and processed, stored and used in the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your Personal Information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to laws of the United States. By using the Service or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer to, and processing, usage, sharing and storage of your information, including Personal Information, in the United States as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

back to top ^
  9. **What Should Parents Know About Children?**

Our Service is intended for a general audience and not directed to Children (i.e., under 13 years of age). If we become aware that we have collected personal information as defined by the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) we will remove or otherwise treat such data as required by COPPA. Any California residents under the age of eighteen (18) who have registered to use the Service, and who have posted content or information on the Service, can request that such information be removed from the Service by contacting us as set forth in Section 7(e) making such a request, stating that they personally posted such content or information and detailing where the content or information is posted. We will make reasonable good faith efforts to remove the post from prospective public view or anonymize it so the minor cannot be individually identified. This removal process cannot ensure complete or comprehensive removal. For instance, third-parties may have republished the post and archived copies of it may be stored by search engines and others that we do not control.

back to top ^
  10. **What About Security?**

We incorporate commercially reasonable safeguards to help protect and secure your Personal Information. However, no data transmission over the Internet, mobile networks, wireless transmission or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us, and you use our Service and provide us with your information at your own risk.

back to top ^
  11. **Changes to the Privacy Policy.**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy prospectively, effective upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy and your use of our Service indicates your consent to the privacy policy posted at the time of use. However, we will not use your previously collected Personal Information in a manner materially different than represented at the time it was collected without your consent. To the extent any provision of this Privacy Policy is found by a competent tribunal to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be severed to the extent necessary for the remainder to be valid and enforceable.

back to top ^
